A Guide to the Edward L. Stone/Borderland Coal Company Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Edward L. Stone Personal Papers
  - National Economic League - letters and bulletins about membership and economic developments of interest to businessmen, 1921 -1932 (Box Box 161)
  - Alexander Hamilton Institute - advertisements for a businessman's informations service, 1928 (Box Box 161)
  - Miss Annie L. Perrow - letters of sympathy on the death of Miss Perrow, Stone's secretary at the Printing Co., 1921 (Box Box 161)
  - 137 National Photo Co. (see also Cahill Iron Works) - photos of unidentified women; advertising samples, ca. 1915 (Box Box 162)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M" - letters of/to Stone's brother Albert to correspondents. Almost all of the letters are to Mercersburg Academy, a boy's school which his son attended, 1912 -1915; (3 folders) (Box Box 162)
  - Richardson-Wayland Electrical Corp. - ads and correspondence about household appliances and service, 1925 -1931 (Box Box 163)
  - E. Henslow Orchard - personal correspondence with this London acquaintance about printing, travel and various pleasures, 1927 -1929 (Box Box 163)
  - 108 Osceola Lodge, #47, Knights of Pythias - about membership and upcoming events, 1921 -1935 (Box Box 163)
  - Miscellaneous "L" - stockholders' information from Leman-Kola Sales Agency, correspondence with W. H. Lewis about management of E. R. Johnson Coal Mining, and literature from the League to Enforce Peace, 1921 -1922 (Box Box 163)
  - 154 Roanoke German Club - Stone was a member of the club and also did some printing jobs for them, 1919 -1934 (Box Box 163)
  - Albert Stone: Miscellaneous "V-Z" - Stone's brother; personal material including YMCA membership, newspaper subscription, etc., 1905 -1914 (Box Box 165)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "M-P", 1905 -1918 (Box Box 165)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "H-L", 1905 -1914 (Box Box 165)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "A-G", 1905 -1914 (Box Box 165)
  - Stocks and bonds - information concerning securities and investments, 1918 -1919; (3 folders) (Box Box 166)
  - Garage - plans, estimates, and correspondence about the remodeling of Stone's garage, 1912; (2 folders) (Box Box 166)
  - Miscellaneous "G"- about fireproofing, home maintenance problems, etc. plus correspondence with P. A. Glasgow, printer, 1909 -1910 (Box Box 166)
  - Miscellaneous "D" - Stone's personal correspondence with old friends and printing associates during his convalescence, 1934 -1936; (4 folders) (Box Box 167)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "H" - personal correspondence and letters about book purchases, hardware purchases, etc., 1900 -1916 (Box Box 168)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "J", 1900 -1916 (Box Box 168)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "S", including especially brochures for steamboat cruises, 1900 -1907 (Box Box 168)
  - A. A. Stone: Miscellaneous "V", 1900 -1916 (Box Box 168)
  - M. F. Stone: miscellaneous letters from Edward Stone to his niece Mary Fred and back about her teaching position and her transfer to a new position, 1899 -1908 (Box Box 168)
  - Virginia Bridge & Iron Co. - company correspondence, reports to stockholders, statements of assets, 1915 -1920; (2 folders) (Box Box 169)
  - Books "Ma-Mc" - letters from book sellers about book offers and catalogues, 1925 -1932 (Box Box 170)
  - Books "Me-Mz" - about offers, purchases, and catalogues from book sellers, 1925 -1932 (Box Box 170)
  - Coal - about purchases of coal to heat his home, 1918 (Box Box 170)
  - Miscellaneous "N" - letters to New York Times about book purchases and premiums from Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1910 -1915 (Box Box 170)
  - Magazines - subscription offers and Stone's responses, 1920 -1921; (2 folders) (Box Box 171)
  - Miscellaneous NS118 - letters about a lost dog, aerial photos, and ads for a "Liberty Starters Corp.", 1919 -1920 (Box Box 171)
  - The Grolier Club - letters to and from the officers of this society of bibliophiles about libraries, exhibitions and collecting, 1923 -1935 (Box Box 172)
  - Mr. and Mrs. T. W. Goodwin and Edmund - early letters concern taxes; later letters are personal, 1918 -1933 (Box Box 172)
  - Fred W. Goudy - personal correspondence with this fellow printing and book lover, 1923 -1933 (Box Box 172)
  - Government Printing Office - about Stone's gift of a U. T. A. code of ethics to be displayed at G. P. O., 1933 -1935 (Box Box 172)
  - Miscellaneous "S" - letters and circulars on many topics, including an order from Scribners, a letter about Southern Industries, etc, all personal concerns, 1931 -1933 (Box Box 172)
  - Manufacturers' Club - agendas, announcements, an; programs for this Philadelphia businessman's club, 1917 -1920 (Box Box 173)
  - Miscellaneous "M" - mostly letters dealing with very routine personal items - drivers licenses, home repairs, chauffeurs uniforms, investment properties, 1910 -1915 (Box Box 173)
  - Mrs. L. Franklin Moore - personal correspondence about travels and health, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 173)
  - Miscellaneous "C" - about book advertisements and an order for a "Baby Oscillator", 1916 (Box Box 173)
  - J. J. Cottrell - letters to Cottrell (agent for Virginia Lines Tariff Bureau) from Stone Printing soliciting his publishing business, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 173)
  - Clippings and comments - about coal industry, southern politics, and inspirational sayings, 1916 (Box Box 173)
  - Miscellaneous "X, Y, Z", - about various matters, like prospective investments which Stone refused, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 173)
  - Y.M.C.A. - about membership, programs, and donations, 1902 -1915 (Box Box 173)
  - Books "Da-Di" - ads, catalogues, and order forms from book dealers, 1921 -1929 (Box Box 174)
  - Books "Do-Dz" - ads, catalogues, and order forms from dealers, 1921 -1929 (Box Box 174)
  - Industrial School for Homeless Boys - appeals for donations, 1920 -1932 (Box Box 174)
  - International Trade Conference - This group aimed at stimulating Southern industry. Stone was an advisor to the exhibition., 1928 (Box Box 174)
  - Young Men's Investment Co. - financial records of this joint stock company which Stone helped to found, 1899 -1910 (Box Box 175)
  - Yama Farms Inn - information about this Japanese-operated country inn, 1914 -1915 (Box Box 175)
  - W. E. Wolfenden Electric Co. - about lighting for Stone's manses, 1905 -1914 (Box Box 175)
  - Dolly Kennedy Yancey - about stock in new investment concerns, 1912 -1914 (Box Box 175)
  - Miscellaneous "W" - requests for oranges, correction on a telephone bill, and a thank you note for a calendar, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 175)
  - Greenbriar - brochures and letters from this Sulphur Springs resort, 1933 -1934 (Box Box 177)
  - Mr. Street (Chas M.) - letters to/from this California attorney friend about personal matters, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 177)
  - Miscellaneous "St" - personal correspondence, especially with family members, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 177)
  - Miscellaneous "Sa-St" - personal correspondence about various printing, household, and health matters, 1930 -1935 (Box Box 177)
  - Worthy Paper Co. - fine paper samples, no date (Box Box 177)
  - C. D. Traphagan - correspondence between Stone and this officer of the U. T. A. about membership and industry matters, 1915 -1917 (Box Box 177)
  - Miscellaneous "X, Y, Z" - Y.M.C.A. programs, etc. - personal letters and memorabilia, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 177)
  - John Wanamaker - Stone's letters to his tailor, 1915 -1919 (Box Box 178)
  - War Work Committee - letters and pamphlets about Stone's involvement in this patriotic organization, 1917 -1913 (Box Box 178)
  - Y.M.C.A. - promotional material and membership information, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 178)
  - Y.W.C.A. - about donations, 1919 (Box Box 178)
  - T - Z 209 (Zee-Zee Tue Co.) - shareholders information, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 178)
  - Miscellaneous "W, X, Y, Z" - various single items about private investments, household repairs, the tanning of a snake skin, and state universities, 1916 -1919 (Box Box 178)
  - Electric Storage Battery Co. - about purchases and use (private) of this company's product, 1905 -1908 (Box Box 179)
  - Electric Vehicle Co. - about personal orders for lamps and fixtures, 1903 -1908 (Box Box 179)
  - Employees - all letters to Stone asking to borrow money (a few ask for raise), 1900 -1916 (Box Box 179)
  - Miscellaneous "E" - chiefly household matters, including Exchange Banking Co., Evening News, Evening World, Engleby Bros. & Co., H. M. Engle, Ellis Bros. Real Estate, Electric Heat Regulator, Eastman Kodak Co., 1900 -1908 (Box Box 179)
  - Virginia Bridge & Iron Co. - about routine business, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 179)
  - Miscellaneous "W" - about household matters, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 179)
  - H. F. Payne (see also American Bank Note Co.) -personal correspondence with this New York friend, and orders to him for playing cards, 1910 Dec -1912 May (Box Box 180)
  - Miscellaneous "P" - letters about personal affairs and private printing interest to: William Pfaff, Henry Porter, T. W. Preston, Mrs. William J. Prout (sister); newsletters, clippings, and letters with or about: The Progressive Printer, politics (house legislation), programmes (music recitals), Printing Trade News, Printers Board of Coal; several letters to Pocahontas Coal & Coke along with letters to hotels, tailors, retailers about personal matters, 1909 -1915; (3 folders) (Box Box 180)
  - Miscellaneous "G" - letters to/from Griggs Packing Co., Mr. Gooch's statements, Edmund G. Gress about books, various personal matters, and a list of the Gooch family's valuable assets, including photos of an old book about Pocahontas, 1916 -1921 (Box Box 180)
  - Books - Virginia History - correspondence with friends, libraries, and dealers about Virginia history books, especially the one on Pocahontas, 1920 (Box Box 180)
  - Miscellaneous "Sa-Se" - letters about Florida real estate, ads (with cloth sample from his tailor), and personal letters to acquaintances, 1924 -1927 (Box Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous "Sh-Sm" - letters from Father Siebert of the parish church, circular concerning a missing person, fruit orders, all personal miscellaneous, 1924 -1928 (Box Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous "So" - including Southern Baptist literature, 1924 -1929 (Box Box 181)
  - Miscellaneous "St-Sw" - requests for stationery, letters to the Country Club, 1924 -1929 (Box Box 181)
  - Printing samples - mainly postcards, but including 3 copies of a history of the Stone Printing Co. complete with pictures of company picnics, etc., 1901 -1910 (Box Box 181)
  - Manufacturers' Club - announcements of upcoming meetings and events, 1911 -1915 (Box Box 182)
  - Public Welfare - Roanoke - letters, surveys, and reports about the establishment of social services in Roanoke, 1928 -1929 (Box Box 182)
  - Pynson Printers, 229 West 43rd St., New York - letters about rare books, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 182)
  - The Quadraginta Club - society of men in the printing business for forty years or more. Stone is the founder. The motto is: "No salaries, no dues, no sad news.", 1924 (Box Box 182)
  - Miscellaneous - a collection of clippings, blank stationery, and speeches, all personal souvenirs, along with a list of Stone's social clubs and business offices, 1922 -1927 (Box Box 183)
  - Typothetae = Educational Dept., Better Printing Company, etc. - about Stone's standing on Better Printing Committee of U.T.A. and his work there, 1925 -1928 (Box Box 183)
  - Association for the Common Good - letters about this civic and state-wide organization, 1920 (Box Box 183)
  - Miscellaneous "V" - about oriental rugs from Vantines, subscription to Vanity Fair, insurance on Virginia Bridge & Iron, 1917 -1934 (Box Box 183)
  - Miscellaneous "S" - assorted private correspondence (e.g. iron business related) with Southern Master Printers, Southern Draft Regulator Co., Southwest Virginia Trust Co., Southwest Virginia, Inc., 1920 -1932 (Box Box 183)
  - Al A. Stone - letters, telegrams, and notes to Stone's brother Al, one-time head of Stone Printing; obituary information gives birth date and life summary, 1923 -1930 (Box Box 184)
  - Dr. Chas. J. Smith - friendly correspondence with Smith, president of Roanoke College, 1924 -1931 (Box Box 184)
  - Southern Master Printers Assoc. - newsletters and announcements, 1921 -1931 (Box Box 184)
  - Books "Aa-Al" - subscription offers, dealers ads, and catalogues, 1930 -1933 (Box Box 184)
  - Books "Am-Az", 1930 -1933 (Box Box 184)
  - Henckel & Co. - letter and book sent gratis from this fellow Virginia printer, 1917 (Box Box 185)
  - Subjects "H" - Hotel Astoria, a book on printing efficiency, and a little printing sample, 1913 (Box Box 185)
  - Miscellaneous "H" - letters (non-business, all for self or household) with: Hamburg American Line (cruises), E. F. Hodson (portable houses), Franklin W. Heath (U. T. A.), Elbert Hubbard (magazine subscription), Don Halsey (politics), 1910 -1914 (Box Box 185)
  - Insurance letters about payment of premiums, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 185)
  - Waldorf Astoria - letters about convention facilities, and guest privileges, 1915 -1919 (Box Box 186)
  - Roanoke War Chest Fund - fund raising letters and newspaper clippings, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 186)
  - Winnemissett Park Co., Deland, Florida - about fruit orders, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 186)
  - Sexton Wilkerson (office) - correspondence about Stone's loan to Sexton to establish an advertising agency, and his advice on the matter, 1910 -1917 (Box Box 186)
  - Miscellaneous "W" - correspondence with (mainly): Woodman 's Oriental Rugs, Frank Webb (Baltimore New Advertising manager), War Map Co., Westmoreland Club, 1914 -1924 (Box Box 186)
  - Menu cards - Stone collected these beautiful menus from restaurants, railroads and conventions, ca. 1914 (Box Box 186)
  - Vollhehr Collection - Collins Bill - clippings and correspondence with a German friend Vollhehr, who in 1932 sold his collection -which included the Gutenberg Bible - to the Library of Congress. The purchase price of $1,500,000 was appropriated under the Collins Bill, 1930 -1932; (2 folders) (Box Box 187)
  - Dr. Otto H. F. Vollhehr - correspondence with Vollhehr about matters unrelated to LC purchase; mostly just "book talk", 1926 -1933; (2 folders) (Box Box 187)
  - Calendar - probably a Stone Printing sample, 1938 (Box Box 187)
  - Mr. Fred Stone - greeting cards and letters to/from this nephew, 1932 -1933 (Box Box 188)
  - Miscellaneous "U-V", including a few U.Va. Newsletters and information on the Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1934 -1935 (Box Box 188)
  - John Clyde Oswald - letters between Stone and this printer/author friend about books and the state of the art, 1914 -1917 (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous "R" - various personal letters, chiefly to the Roycroft School and to some Florida hotels, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 189)
  - Roanoke Hospital - about donations, 1915 Dec -1918 Feb (Box Box 189)
  - William Pfaff - personal correspondence with this printer-friend from New Orleans, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous - Stone apparently despaired of ever filing this assortment of tailor samples, cablegrams, and invitations, 1913 -1917 (Box Box 189)
  - Photographs, ca. 1918 (Box Box 189)
  - Manufacturers Record Publishing Co. - about magazine subscriptions, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 189)
  - W. E. Mingea - about purchase of coal properties in Mingo County, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 189)
  - J. Horace McFarland (see American Civic Assoc.) about civic affairs and printing innovations, 1911 -1914 (Box Box 189)
  - Mill Mountain Incline - about mortgages on this mountain property, 1914 (Box Box 189)
  - Miscellaneous "M" - unsorted ads, subscription forms, etc. from companies, 1913 -1914 (Box Box 189)
  - Mlasovsky & Wagner - tailors; file including catalogues, cloth samples and correspondence about suits, 1910 -1913 (Box Box 189)
  - Albert W. Finlay - friendly correspondence about state of printing industry during the war (petition to have it declared "essential", etc.), 1918 -1919 (Box Box 190)
  - E. B. Fishburn - correspondence with these New York stationers, 1900 -1903 (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G" with: Mrs. G. G. Gooch, Goodspeeds Book Shop, W. A. R Goodwin, Carter Glass, A. M. Glassbrenner, James J. Gilliam, 1935 -1936 (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous "S" - including receipt for a fountain etc., 1915 (Box Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous "W" - notices from publishers, and letters to friends, 1935 -1936 April; (2 folders) (Box Box 190)
  - Books: "Ha" - catalogues, offers, and order forms from publishers, 1928-1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 191)
  - Book "He-Ho", 1928 -1935 (Box Box 191)
  - Books "Hu", 1928 -1935 (Box Box 191)
  - Books "I-J", 1928 -1935 (Box Box 191)
  - National Assoc. of Manufacturers - letters about state of American industry during war and relevant legislation, 1917 -1918 (Box Box 192)
  - National Exchange Bank - invitations to Board of Directors meetings and receipts for Liberty Bonds, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous "Ni" - newsletters and ads, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous "W" - personal letters, especially with: Waldorf Astoria, Whitaker & Co. (tailors - samples including), John Wanamaker (jeweler), 1912 -1915 (Box Box 192)
  - James P. Woods - Woods seems to have been Stone's attorney at this time, and the letters concern business affairs, dividing stock, etc., 1909 -1915 (Box Box 192)
  - National Industrial Conference Board - promotional literature for National Industrial Board, 1919 (Box Box 192)
  - National Foreign Trade Council - promotional literature, 1919 (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous "N" - promotional literature from: National City Bank, National Railroad Operators Assoc., Nelson Doubleday Inc., National Exchange Bank of Roanoke, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 192)
  - Miscellaneous ''Aa-Al" - letters, ads, orders - all related to personal and household affairs (pipe organs, gardening, auto insurance), 1924 -1928 (Box Box 193)
  - Miscellaneous ''Am'', 1924 -1928 (Box Box 193)
  - Miscellaneous "An-Ax", 1924 -1928 (Box Box 193)
  - National Exchange Bank - business about the board of directors, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 194)
  - Miscellaneous "D" - ads and letters from everyone, from Deitrich Distillers to Dr. Deimel Underwear (Linen - mesh); all personal business and household purchases, 1905 -1909 (Box Box 197)
  - Miscellaneous "A-E" - personal orders to local drug store, bicycle shop, etc., 1913 -1918 (Box Box 200)
  - War Relief Fund - requests for assistance from various agencies providing war relief; all appeared to have gone unanswered, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 200)
  - Rotary Club of Roanoke - announcements of meetings and rotary club literature, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 200)
  - Miscellaneous "La" - captains junk mail - from charities, businesses, national organizations, and booksellers, 1920 -1930 (Box Box 201)
  - Miscellaneous "Le'', 1920 -1930 (Box Box 201)
  - Miscellaneous "Li", 1920 -1930 (Box Box 201)
  - Miscellaneous "Lo-Ly", 1920 -1930 (Box Box 201)
  - Office furniture - catalogues, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 202)
  - Miscellaneous "O'' - personal correspondence and ads related to car trouble, auto tires, open shop printing and various other subjects, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 202)
  - Post cards - some are from friends but most are blank and appear to have been collected as printing samples, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 202)
  - Miscellaneous "P" - correspondence and literature with and about: Payne Tariff Bill, Patent ads, R. D. Parker (employee), Pacific Monthly, People's Furniture Co., prohibition, C. E. Postlethwaite, Dr. Pole, Pitzer Transfer Co., George W. Payne (tailors), People's National Bank of Lynchburg, Everett Perkins, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 202)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop - correspondence about searches for rare books, and condition and delivery of books ordered, 1926 -1931 (Box Box 204)
  - Houghton-Mifflin Co. - correspondence about book purchases, 1925 -1928 (Box Box 204)
  - William A. Hildebrand, 1923 -1929 (Box Box 204)
  - Bernard Halliday - books, 1924 -1925 (Box Box 204)
  - W. Heffer & Son, Ltd. - books, including invoices and receipts, 1925 -1926 (Box Box 204)
  - A. J. Huston - including catalogue, 1926 (Box Box 204)
  - Martin Hopkinson & Co. - catalogue and book offers only; no correspondence, no date (Box Box 204)
  - Charles F. Heartman - correspondence about the sale of books, 1931 -1932 (Box Box 204)
  - Red Cross - correspondence about war relief fund, lists of business in Roanoke and people to contact, and a small glass plate used probably for printing fund raising material, 1917 -1918; (2 folders) (Box Box 205)
  - Roanoke Times - balance sheets and year end statements to stockholders; Stone was probably a leading stockholder, 1915 -1918 (Box Box 205)
  - National Assoc. of Owners of Railroad Securities clippings, circular letters, ads about safety of securities and legislation affecting them, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 205)
  - National Citizens League - letter drafting Stone for membership and promotional material on the League, 1912 -1918 (Box Box 205)
  - T-Z 129 - letters to artists, fruit sellers, ads for military training camps, 1915 -1919 (Box Box 205)
  - Mlasovsky & Wagner - ads from tailor, 1916 -1917 (Box Box 205)
  - National Assoc. of Manufacturers - bulletins and brochures from N. A. M. about industry and the war, 1918 -1920 (Box Box 205)
  - Miscellaneous "N-S" 128 - letters to various businesses about orders, congratulations, deliveries, etc., 1918 -1920 (Box Box 205)
  - Relief fund - requests for financial aid from a variety of charities - the Lafayette Fund for Disabled French Vets to the Montreat (N.C.) Auditorium drive; no replies sent, 1918 (Box Box 207)
  - Red Cross - newsletters and a receipt for a $2 membership fee, 1918 (Box Box 207)
  - Pittsburgh Typothetae, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania - announcements of upcoming events, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 207)
  - Miscellaneous "T-Z" 149 - tailors, time tables, valves for steam, etc., 1917 (Box Box 207)
  - Roanoke Automobile Assoc. - membership promotion and Stone's reply to their effort, 1916 -1918 (Box Box 207)
  - Miscellaneous "N-S" 148 - prisoners' relief, Presbyterian orphans, William Prout's radishes, 1916 -1920 (Box Box 207)
  - Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco - about graphic arts display at a Knoxville Exposition, 1912 -1913 (Box Box 207)
  - People's National Bank - loan offers from the bank to Stone, 1912 -1917 (Box Box 207)
  - Printers mark - E.L.S. - sketches of a self styled printers mark of Stone's, with a description and all relevant correspondence, 1931 (Box Box 208)
  - William Pfaff, New Orleans, Louisiana -correspondence about printing, rare books, their families, their health, 1924 -1934 (Box Box 208)
  - Dr. F. V. M. Painter - about books on the labor unions, 1921 (Box Box 208)
  - Magazines - subscription offers, 1930 -1932 (Box Box 208)
  - J. W. Hancock - correspondence covers the two friends many interests, including Edgar Allen Poe, the Grolier Club, and book collecting, 1921 -1936 (Box Box 208)
  - Frederick U. Hamilton - about textbooks for printers apprentices, 1915 (Box Box 208)
  - Books "C-D" - letters to booksellers: Montgomery Cooper, Cheswick Press, Dorr Kimball, R. V. Coleman about orders, 1925 -1931 (Box Box 208)
  - Books: invoices and receipts "A-C", 1925 -1935 (Box Box 209)
  - Books: invoices and receipts "D-L", 1925 -1935 (Box Box 209)
  - Books: invoices and receipts "M-Q", 1925 -1935 (Box Box 209)
  - Books: invoices and receipts "R-Z", 1925 -1935 (Box Box 209)
  - John A. Coughlin - about a Stone Printing job done for Coughlin, 1913 -1914 (Box Box 210)
  - Chestnut Ridge property - about improvements on Stone's Chestnut Ridge property, 1913 -1914 (Box Box 210)